<publicwhip>
	<regmem personid="uk.org.publicwhip/person/10001" membername="Diane Abbott" date="2021-12-13">
		<category type="1" name="Employment and earnings">
			<record>
				<item>
					Payments from the Guardian, Kings Place, 90 York Way, London N1 9GU, for articles:
				</item>
				<item>
					24 July 2020, received £100. Hours: 1 hr. (Registered 02 February 2021)
				</item>
				<item>
					19 October 2020, received £258.80. Hours: 1 hr 30 mins. (Registered 02 February 2021)
				</item>
				<item>
					18 March 2021, received £300 for contribution to an article. Hours: 1.5 hrs. (Registered 23 March 2021)
				</item>
				<item>
					5 May 2021, received £100 for an article published on 22 April 2021. Hours: 45 mins. (Registered 07 June 2021)
				</item>
				<item>
					24 November 2020, received £200 from the BBC, Portland Place, London W1A 1AA, for an appearance on Any Questions on 13 November 2020. Hours: 1.5 hrs. (Registered 08 February 2021)
				</item>
				<item>
					17 March 2021, received £18,450 from Viking Penguin, 20 Vauxhall Bridge Rd, London SW1V 2SA, via Blake Friedmann Literary, TV &amp; Film Agency Ltd, Ground Floor, 15 Highbury Place, London N5 1QP, by way of an advance for a book. Hours: 80 hrs to date. (Registered 24 March 2021)
				</item>
				<item>
					4 July 2021, received £400 from Operation Black Vote, 18A Victoria Park Square, Bethnal Green, London E2 9PB, for delivering a presentation on 12 May 2021. Hours: 2 hrs. (Registered 02 August 2021)
				</item>
			</record>
		</category>
		<category type="4" name="Visits outside the UK">
			<record>
				<item>
					Name of donor: GUBA Foundation
					<br>
						Address of donor: 459 Prince Regent Lane, London E16 3HX
					</br>
					<br>
						Estimate of the probable value (or amount of any donation): International flights £805.07; accommodation £1,461.05; GUBA Awards event ticket £365.39; total value £2,631.51
					</br>
					<br>Destination of visit: Accra, Ghana</br>
					<br>Dates of visit: 5-12 November 2021</br>
					<br>
						Purpose of visit: To participate in the GUBA Foundation Yaa Asantewaa Womens Empowerment Awards ceremony and meet other relevant civil society organisations.
					</br>
					<br>(Registered 16 November 2021)</br>
				</item>
			</record>
		</category>
		<category type="8" name="Miscellaneous">
			<record>
				<item>
					Since December 2015, a trustee of the Diane Abbott Foundation, which works to excel and improve education. (Registered 26 October 2016)
				</item>
			</record>
		</category>
	</regmem>
	<regmem personid="uk.org.publicwhip/person/25034" membername="Debbie Abrahams" date="2021-12-13">
		<category type="8" name="Miscellaneous">
			<record>
				<item>
					Along with the Good Law Project and two other MPs, since 6 October 2020 I have been party to judicial review proceedings crowdfunded through the Good Law Project, 3 East Point High Street, Seal, Sevenoaks, TN15 0EG. Total costs incurred on this action: £98,914.42. £85,000 was paid by the government, leaving the remainder (£13,914.42) payable by GLP direct to Counsel. (Registered 27 October 2020; updated 26 January 2021 and 28 April 2021)
				</item>
			</record>
		</category>
	</regmem>
	<regmem personid="uk.org.publicwhip/person/24878" membername="Nigel Adams" date="2021-12-13">
		<category type="3" name="Gifts, benefits and hospitality from UK sources">
			<record>
				<item>
					Name of donor: Betting and Gaming Council (BGC)
					<br>Address of donor: 16 Smith Square, London SW1P 3HU</br>
					<br>
						Amount of donation or nature and value if donation in kind: Ticket with hospitality to attend the Euro 2020 tournament, value £1,999.14
					</br>
					<br>Date received: 18 June 2021</br>
					<br>Date accepted: 18 June 2021</br>
					<br>Donor status: company, registration 12213577</br>
					<br>(Registered 16 July 2021)</br>
				</item>
				<item>
					Name of donor: Power Leisure Bookmakers Ltd
					<br>
						Address of donor: Waterfront, Chancellors Road, London W6 9HP
					</br>
					<br>
						Amount of donation or nature and value if donation in kind: Ticket with hospitality to attend the Euro 2020 tournament, value £1,961
					</br>
					<br>Date received: 29 June 2021</br>
					<br>Date accepted: 29 June 2021</br>
					<br>Donor status: company, registration 03822566</br>
					<br>(Registered 02 August 2021)</br>
				</item>
				<item>
					Name of donor: Entain Holdings UK
					<br>Address of donor: One New Change, London EC4M 9AF</br>
					<br>
						Amount of donation or nature and value if donation in kind: Ticket with hospitality to attend the Euro 2020 tournament, value £3,457
					</br>
					<br>Date received: 7 July 2021</br>
					<br>Date accepted: 7 July 2021</br>
					<br>Donor status: company, registration 03822566</br>
					<br>(Registered 03 August 2021)</br>
				</item>
				<item>
					Name of donor: Heineken UK Ltd
					<br>Address of donor: The Brewery, Tadcaster LS24 9SA</br>
					<br>
						Amount of donation or nature and value if donation in kind: Ticket with hospitality to attend the Euro 2020 tournament, approx. value £620
					</br>
					<br>Date received: 11 July 2021</br>
					<br>Date accepted: 11 July 2021</br>
					<br>Donor status: company, registration SC065527</br>
					<br>(Registered 06 August 2021)</br>
				</item>
			</record>
		</category>
		<category type="6" name="Land and property portfolio: (i) value over £100,000 and/or (ii) giving rental income of over £10,000 a year">
			<record>
				<item>
					One mixed use commercial and residential property in Selby, North Yorkshire, co-owned with my wife: (i) and (ii).
				</item>
				<item>
					Three residential properties in York co-owned with my wife, the second of which was acquired in September 2017, and the third on 1 October 2021: (i) and (ii). (Registered 13 May 2015; updated 10 October 2017 and 02 November 2021)
				</item>
				<item>
					From 18 March 2016, one residential property in Leeds co-owned with my wife: (i) and from 10 May 2016 (ii). (Registered 18 March 2016; updated 10 May 2016)
				</item>
			</record>
		</category>
		<category type="9" name="Family members employed and paid from parliamentary expenses">
			<record>
				<item>
					I employ my spouse, Claire Adams, as part-time Office Manager.
				</item>
			</record>
		</category>
	</regmem>
	<regmem personid="uk.org.publicwhip/person/25661" membername="Bim Afolami" date="2021-12-13">
		<category type="1" name="Employment and earnings">
			<record>
				<item>
					From 27 November 2020 until further notice, non-executive director of Apprentify Limited, Crown House, Manchester Road, Wilmslow, SK9 1BH, an organisation which helps provide apprenticeships to young people. I receive £2,500 per month for an expected commitment of 8–10 hours per month. (Registered 07 December 2020)
				</item>
				<item>
					Payment of £1,000 expected from DMG Media Ltd/Associated Newspapers Ltd, Northcliffe House, 2 Derry St, Kensington, London W8 5TT, for an article written for the Mail on Sunday on 24 October 2020. Hours: 3 hrs. (Registered 22 December 2020)
				</item>
			</record>
		</category>
		<category type="2" name="(b) Any other support not included in Category 2(a)">
			<record>
				<item>
					Name of donor: Hitchin and Harpenden Portcullis Club
					<br>Address of donor: PO Box 1241, Harpenden AL1 9JF</br>
					<br>
						Amount of donation or nature and value if donation in kind: £10,000
					</br>
					<br>Date received: 15 November 2021</br>
					<br>Date accepted: 15 November 2021</br>
					<br>Donor status: unincorporated association</br>
					<br>(Registered 25 November 2021)</br>
				</item>
			</record>
		</category>
		<category type="8" name="Miscellaneous">
			<record>
				<item>
					Member (unpaid) of the Ditchley Foundation's Programme Committee. (Registered 06 July 2017)
				</item>
				<item>
					From June 2017, Member (unpaid) of the Court of the University of Bedfordshire. (Registered 30 January 2018)
				</item>
				<item>
					From 13 September 2018, Member (unpaid) of the Financial Inclusion Commission, a cross-party organisation which supports the principle of increased financial inclusion in the UK. (Registered 21 September 2018)
				</item>
				<item>
					From 22 October 2018, Trustee (unpaid) of the Mitsubishi UFJ Trust Oxford Foundation, which supports the Oxford Union Literary and Debating Trust and through it the charitable activities of the Oxford Union Society. (Registered 05 November 2018)
				</item>
			</record>
		</category>
	</regmem>
	<regmem personid="uk.org.publicwhip/person/11929" membername="Adam Afriyie" date="2021-12-13">
		<category type="7" name="(i) Shareholdings: over 15% of issued share capital">
			<record>
				<item>
					From 23 June 2021, Baubridge Limited. (Registered 08 November 2021)
				</item>
			</record>
		</category>
	</regmem>
	<regmem personid="uk.org.publicwhip/person/25822" membername="Imran Ahmad Khan" date="2021-12-13">
		<category type="1" name="Employment and earnings">
			<record>
				<item>
					3 February 2021, received £3,000 from Bindmans LLP (law firm), 236 Gray’s Inn Road, London WC1X 8HB, for participation in a fact finding panel into the detention of Prince Mohammed Bin Nayef and Prince Ahmed Abdelaziz Al Saud. Hours: approx. 50 hrs. (Registered 09 February 2021)
				</item>
			</record>
		</category>
		<category type="6" name="Land and property portfolio: (i) value over £100,000 and/or (ii) giving rental income of over £10,000 a year">
			<record>
				<item>
					From 1 March 2020, a flat in London: (i) and (ii). (Registered 20 May 2020)
				</item>
			</record>
		</category>
	</regmem>
	<regmem personid="uk.org.publicwhip/person/25817" membername="Nickie Aiken" date="2021-12-13">
		<category type="3" name="Gifts, benefits and hospitality from UK sources">
			<record>
				<item>
					<strong>
						<em>
							Name of donor: UK Music Ltd
							<br>
								Address of donor: Savoy Hill House, 7- 10 Savoy Hill, London WC2R 0BU
							</br>
							<br>
								Amount of donation or nature and value if donation in kind: Ticket to the Brit Awards, value £900
							</br>
							<br>Date received: 11 May 2021</br>
							<br>Date accepted: 11 May 2021</br>
							<br>Donor status: company, registration 03245288</br>
							<br>(Registered 01 July 2021)</br>
							<br>
								This is a late entry to which the rectification procedure was applied on 29 September 2021. Paragraph 15 of chapter 4 of the Guide to the Rules refers.
							</br>
						</em>
					</strong>
				</item>
				<item>
					On 22 October 2021, I accepted honorary membership of the Carlton Club for the duration of my time as the MP for the Cities of London and Westminster. (Registered 01 November 2021)
				</item>
			</record>
		</category>
		<category type="4" name="Visits outside the UK">
			<record>
				<item>
					Name of donor: Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Qatar
					<br>
						Address of donor: Qatar Embassy, 1 South Audley Street, London W1K 1NB
					</br>
					<br>
						Estimate of the probable value (or amount of any donation): Flights, accommodation, internal travel, and meals with a value of £7,523.67
					</br>
					<br>Destination of visit: Qatar</br>
					<br>Dates of visit: 12-17 October 2021</br>
					<br>
						Purpose of visit: British-Qatari APPG visit to meet ministers and officials to discuss Qatar's humanitarian and political response to the Afghanistan crisis, preparations for the World Cup, workers' rights reform and bilateral relations.
					</br>
					<br>(Registered 01 November 2021)</br>
				</item>
			</record>
		</category>
		<category type="8" name="Miscellaneous">
			<record>
				<item>
					Unpaid director of Sprucespace Ltd, a freehold management company. (Registered 08 January 2020)
				</item>
			</record>
		</category>
	</regmem>
</publicwhip>